I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to stay on track of
my fitness goals. Here are the seven low
calorie, high protein ninja creamy pints
I made this week. Started it off with a
frosted animal cookie blizzard. This is
a Dairy Queen recreation. They sadly
discontinued this a couple years ago, so
you're welcome for bringing it back.
I've gotten tons of requests for fall
flavors. So, I started off with the
apple pie flavor. It's a cinnamon base
with apple pie filling as a mixin. If
you like apple pie, you would love this
one. Continuing the fall trend, I did a
pumpkin cheesecake flavor. So, this was
a pumpkin cheesecake base topped with
some crumbled graham cracker. One of the
thickest bases I have ever made. It took
some serious force to get it out. Then I
did a brand deal with Milk 50 and I made
an Oreo McFlurry using their milk. Like
I've always said, if I ever do a brand
deal, it's because the product is
actually good. This was amazing. Then I
continued my series where I recreate Ben
& Jerry's flavors. This was everything
but the one of my all-time favorites. I
had my parents try it and they said it
was the best flavor I have ever made.
Then I started a new series on the
channel where I recreate seasonal
treats. This was caramel apple. I can't
believe how similar it tasted to a
caramel apple. It was insane. And then
in honor of Fuel Snacks restocking their
protein cookie dough, I had to run back
my cookie dough ice cream. This one just
hits every single time.